

ABOUT

I have saturated half-year experience with programming web-applications. I want to become a strong developer in the shortest time. In this way I'm spending a lot of time for selfeducation and trying to be always in progress. In addition, I can easily and with joy become a part of the team.

CONTACTS







+38 063 234 35 24



ruslan-z1



zinchenko.rusya@gmail.com



linkedin.com/RuslanZinchenko



facebook.com/RuslanZinchenko



RUSLAN ZINCHENKO

Front-End Developer

PORTFOLIOS



Calorie Burner

Home fitness app for people who don't have free time to exercise.

https://calorieburner https://test.goit.co.ua



Language Tests

Tests in three programming languages: Java, C#. Java Script.



FindPic

Application for searching pictures by using API of pexels.com.

https://findpic



SK WEAR

Swimwear online store.

https://skwearonline

SKILLS

Professional

HTML5 **CSS3 RESTful API JavaScript**

React.js Vue.js GIT **XALA**

Language

English - intermediate

EXPERIENCE

Knauf

PC Operator, Sales Manager September 2009 - March 2020 PC Operator, Construction Sales Manager. Formation of invoices and documents for loading transport from dealerships. Consultation on the presence of goods in warehouses.

Pravex Bank

PC Operator September 2007 - May 2009 Document management department, e-mail and fax center.

INTEREST



Computers (inside)



Programming



Football



Music



Traveling



Self-education

EDUCATION

Full-Stack WEB Developer

GoIT school -Ukraine since April 2018 Upgrading skills with HTML5/CSS3, Vanilla JS, Node.js, React.js, GULP, WebPack.

QA engineer

SkillUp - Ukraine since January 2018 QA programming courses (HTML, CSS, SQL).

Process Engineer

University "Ukraine"
Sep 2002 - Sep 2007
Faculty of
Engineering
Technologies,
engineer in the field
of electronics and
telecommunications.

Online CV